[{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974991062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":18023,"timeElapsed":136607},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975005936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":14872,"timeElapsed":151481},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975016751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":10813,"timeElapsed":162297},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975024532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7779,"timeElapsed":170078},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975032259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":7725,"timeElapsed":177805},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975040335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8075,"timeElapsed":185881},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975047659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7321,"timeElapsed":193205},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975059050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11389,"timeElapsed":204596},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975072215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":13163,"timeElapsed":217761},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975084698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":10101,"timeElapsed":230244},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975096552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":11852,"timeElapsed":242098},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975105797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9244,"timeElapsed":251343},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975110611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4813,"timeElapsed":256157},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975130870,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":20257,"timeElapsed":276416},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975137477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6604,"timeElapsed":283023},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975143734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6256,"timeElapsed":289280},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975147921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4185,"timeElapsed":293466},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975154936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7014,"timeElapsed":300482},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975159945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5008,"timeElapsed":305491},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975174174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":11683,"timeElapsed":319720},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975180155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5979,"timeElapsed":325701},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975190484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":10328,"timeElapsed":336030},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975195522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5036,"timeElapsed":341068},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975212532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":17008,"timeElapsed":358078},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975221445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":8911,"timeElapsed":366991},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975225830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4384,"timeElapsed":371376},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975234204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8372,"timeElapsed":379750},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975238257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4052,"timeElapsed":383803},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975262715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":22756,"timeElapsed":408261},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975266185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":3468,"timeElapsed":411730},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975274149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7963,"timeElapsed":419695},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975278203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4052,"timeElapsed":423749},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975285968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":7764,"timeElapsed":431514},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975292305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":6335,"timeElapsed":437851},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975296711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4404,"timeElapsed":442257},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975304121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":7408,"timeElapsed":449667},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975306836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2714,"timeElapsed":452382},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975318553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":9563,"timeElapsed":464099},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975323291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":4736,"timeElapsed":468836},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975330638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7346,"timeElapsed":476184},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975335215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4575,"timeElapsed":480761},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975341451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":6235,"timeElapsed":486997},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975349517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":8065,"timeElapsed":495063},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975354677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5158,"timeElapsed":500223},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975361427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6749,"timeElapsed":506973},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975366164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4735,"timeElapsed":511710},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975380921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":13168,"timeElapsed":526467},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975386573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5651,"timeElapsed":532119},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975393790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":7215,"timeElapsed":539336},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975398145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":4353,"timeElapsed":543691},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975404237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6091,"timeElapsed":549783},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975410401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":6163,"timeElapsed":555947},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975416273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":5870,"timeElapsed":561819},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975421969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":5694,"timeElapsed":567515},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975425840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3869,"timeElapsed":571386},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975438271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":10448,"timeElapsed":583817},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975446628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8355,"timeElapsed":592174},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975451593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4963,"timeElapsed":597139},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975454992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3398,"timeElapsed":600538},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975461006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6012,"timeElapsed":606552},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975465079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4071,"timeElapsed":610625},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975469212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4131,"timeElapsed":614758},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975475718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":6504,"timeElapsed":621264},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975479258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3539,"timeElapsed":624804},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975494655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":13957,"timeElapsed":640201},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975500378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":5722,"timeElapsed":645924},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975505729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":5349,"timeElapsed":651275},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975508676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2945,"timeElapsed":654222},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975512739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4062,"timeElapsed":658285},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975516904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4163,"timeElapsed":662450},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975522678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":5773,"timeElapsed":668224},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975528210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5530,"timeElapsed":673756},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975532436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4224,"timeElapsed":677982},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975558840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":24934,"timeElapsed":704386},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975564915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6073,"timeElapsed":710461},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975572318,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7401,"timeElapsed":717864},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975584785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":12465,"timeElapsed":730331},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975589339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":4553,"timeElapsed":734885},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975594389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":5048,"timeElapsed":739935},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975599749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5359,"timeElapsed":745295},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975605712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5962,"timeElapsed":751258},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975615429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":9715,"timeElapsed":760975},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975620728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5298,"timeElapsed":766274},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975637113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":15014,"timeElapsed":782659},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975642052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4937,"timeElapsed":787598},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975654469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":12415,"timeElapsed":800015},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975660684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6214,"timeElapsed":806230},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975667150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6465,"timeElapsed":812696},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975671886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4735,"timeElapsed":817432},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975677157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5269,"timeElapsed":822703},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975683411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6253,"timeElapsed":828957},{"subjectID":"bh0ulsj0gx","prolificID":"66fad26e4b07f6149ceb136d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d6d7e63f6434a42db84","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975687778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4364,"timeElapsed":833323}]